Investment in market securities is
subject to market risk. All the
documents should be carefully
reviewed before investing in PVR Anox.
This is a negative news because if you look at PV
Anox, it is already facing a lot of problems. There is no
movement in the stock price. Who really had much hope from this
stock? When the merger of PV Anox took place, it
seemed like a
type of monopoly business. But in this
era of OTT, in this competition,
we still do not have profitability-wise theaters. It is
visible that of
course some blockbusters come, but if they are
taken, the cinema earns, so the picture earns,
but PVR Anox cannot earn
and if such orders come from above, then there
is a problem because this was brought by one state
government, tomorrow another state
government will bring it, then it will be a big problem for these people.
And of course, let's
say that this will cause a volume pickup, people will go to
see more films. Now, that will happen when it happens,
but the direct impact will come to these people
.  You see, the way these people
sell popcorn and Pepsi in FNB, their
income is increasing a little bit.  The
counter income from cinemas, that is, tickets, is
not that much, so the real margin is the
cold drinks sold to these people, like popcorn,
but the overall impact will be good
and this will create more problems for them. If you
look at this, those people
are in the continuous expansion plan, still their loss was almost
238 crores. Now, going forward, they
want to adopt the capital light model strategy, they want to bring more than 200 screens,
but the way this type of people are coming up with
rules and in which they have
100% control, it is negative for Piva Anox
.  I am overall negative about drinking anoxic
for the long term and want to avoid this counter
.   Let's take
a look at the coat because
yesterday you saw a very positive action. Nifty
gainer, Effendo gainer, this counter was a big
corp that we have seen buying because the
outlook of the company for 26 has been
very strong. After that, there was a great
boom. How can you advise us here?
Fundamentals
If you look at the monthly
numbers that are coming, auto numbers, if we
see a good increase in Hero Monter,
we can almost say that the volume has
increased by 17%, which is very good.
And today, the monsoon is increasing, as the
report cut is going to come forward, I
think there will be an increase here,
especially in this country, we can expect double digit gains.
When the Diwali
season starts in November, the festival
season comes in a good way.  Again, this
stock is not that old. If we compare it to its
peers, TVS Motor Cab is not all that bad,
but it is quite low compared to TVS. Even Asha has also
performed well.  As
you know, Hero Motors is doing well in the ruler area
and that's where their products
sell the most. I think there will be a
revival of sorts and from here,
people are expanding their EV portfolios
there too.
So even there, if you look at the EV seals, the
Motop ones are coming in pretty good.  I think these two to three
months will be good for the No. 2 buyers,
so we can say that Hero Motor is of one type
that we will be a beneficiary of this
flow and from here also I feel that if
someone stays for a little longer than six months or a year then I think
you
can hold Hero Motocop. I am seeing an increase from here.
I am
also focusing today. I want to take your view on
Dixon Tech because the
update that the company is showing today is positive. The
company is firstly getting news of acquisition. It has
acquired 51% stake in Qtech India
and along with that, the company is
focusing today. The news is also positive
that it is entering a new business.
Dixon Tech has now entered the camera and fingerprint
module. Multiple
bullish brokerage reports are also showing us coming.
Right now, look at the pre-open bit. It has
not settled but right now, the gap up is  We are seeing
signs of opening.
A view from Dixon Tech and
how are you viewing this news for the company? Tapan Aap,
this news is very good for the company and
Actual Dixon Technology is such a company
that is in the headlines every day. Somehow, some
upgrade or downgrade keeps coming in this stock.
But you ask the same question to a
fundamental analyst, how do you
feel? He will always say that it is expensive.
But even though this stock is expensive, it is
giving growth. This is a difference
because if you look at the stock, if it has a P value above 100, it
always seems expensive. But one thing is that if there is
growth, there is no problem and the way it has
orders, strong orders, it is
good for exports.
Even the operating cash flow has improved a lot
.  If I talk about the stock, some
negatives that were coming earlier, Motorola's deal
loss was a negative, but here it
seems that these people are doing
a good standing in their ODM business
and are also doing backward integration
and are moving forward in the EV and industrial
EMS segments.
EMS segment is going to be a very big sector going
forward, our
penetration is around 4% now, 3 to 4% in two to
three years, it will be around 8%. If we
talk about China Plus One policy, then EMS
segment will be the biggest beneficiary and in
EMS too, if the next biggest one is working, then
this is the same. Dicken Technology is the
second one. If I go and see,
these people are increasing their capacity in mobile IT and hardware, so
all the
news is positive. So on this stock, I will
say only one thing, if you have it,
hold it 100%, the weight should be reduced, but the
valuation that is there will always be a good one
because it comes in the premium segment, so it
comes in the premium valuation, but according to me, this is a
total hole. The way the news is flowing from here,
I think it can increase from here
.  We saw a lot of strength in the wire segment,
industrials had a
strong Polycab counter, if we look at
Fendo, apart from this,
Finolex is capable of generating RR from cash, we also saw a
strength there.
How would you give a view for this segment and this sector and
fundamentally do you see any company as strong?
From here,
if this segment is one, then a
transition phase is going on in it as
Adani and Billa have said that we are
making an entry. Still, those people have a very
small business but in the next one or two years, those
people are also going to come here in full flight because
those people also want to move forward in industrial
development, they can say industrial, in
infrastructure. Right now, if we look at
Polycable, RR Cable, and all of them are doing well,
and you are also
seeing good results, then I think that
from here, it will not matter for three or four quarters.
These people's business will be good.
But one caveat that I would like to add here is that these
big players who enter will have to
see if there will be any compression in the margins. If you
look at me here, I will
increase the Polycap.  The year is starting to look up, the decline is starting to look up,
even in a two-year counter,
as I said, we will have to see if
you look at the volume of all of them, then the growth has been almost in
double digits. If we
go over the sector as a whole, then the growth has been 24%. It is very
good. Even if the cost of copper and
aluminum is causing
some margin pressure, but these
people are maintaining it, increasing capex. Everyone is increasing capex
because when two big
players come, everyone will be alert and
can increase capex. Then there will be
some impact on ROC. Competition will
increase a little. That is why I
am positive in the medium term. In the long term, as I said,
my special focus will be on Adani and Billa. The
investment advice is in the medium term. In the
long term, we will have to see a little. In this, let's
take a view for Lombard for CGI.
Tapan, after the results, because the
company's profit has increased by 29%.  The 14%
increase in premium is showing us
how this quarter will look.
Overall, as an insurance businessman, I
am quite positive because if you wait for the results, then if it goes well, there will be
no such issue and of course, it will
increase going forward because if you look at their profit side, in
all respects, their premium side has
jumped by 44%, which is quite a lot. Let me
talk about retail health premium. Now again, if the
pressure on the margins of those people came
because their expenses had increased, but the
management has also talked about that, they will
bring the motor claims under control. In all of that, we
can say that the claim pass has increased. I
think profitability is also being hit,
but it will normalize going forward. I
think that the motor premium will
increase by 14-15% from here and the premium at the end of the day will
also increase.  If it should increase by almost 15.1%, then if
we look at it this way, it
seems that there may be a slight increase. Of course, those
people have got a little capital gain momentum.
Recently,
going forward in this quarter, the retail health segment, which is still
under-penetrated in India, will increase significantly. If we
talk about health insurance, those
people will benefit from this and even
underwriting and the combined ratio are
also under control. So, looking at all this, I
feel that once those people
bring some efficiency in the expense ratio, they will
get better results from here.  I
am positive that if anyone has this stock,
we can hold it. The insurance
sector as a whole, I think, will
give decent returns for a few years. Even if it does
not outperform, it can give a decent return.